Guide to the Robert Prosky papers, 1909-2007
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Robert Prosky Papers
1909-2007
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives
Robert Prosky, 1930-2008
9 linear feet (16 boxes)
Consists of documents spanning Prosky's career in theatre, film, and television. Materials include playbills, photographs, scripts, reviews, fan letters, scrapbooks, and audiovisual.
C0022
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Robert Prosky in 2007-2008.
Biographical Information
Born in Philadelphia, Robert Prosky (1930-2008) spent much of his career as an actor in more than 200 plays at the Arena Stage in Washington, D.C., on Broadway in New York City, and in regional theatre. Prosky's association with the Arena Stage included more than 130 productions over the course of 20 years. His Broadway appearances included "Glengarry Glenross," "A Walk in the Woods," and "A View from the Bridge." Highlights from regional theater include "Death of a Salesman," "Twelfth Night," and "You Can't Take It With You." He also performed on stage in the Moscow Art Theatre in Russia, the Gate Theater in Dublin, Ireland, as well as in a Chinese theater in Hong Kong.
Beginning in the 1980s, he began regularly appearing in films and television shows. His films include "Mrs. Doubtfire," "The Natural," and "Dead Man Walking." Television credits include three years on "Hill Street Blues," many television films and guest shots.
He received or was nominated for two Tony awards, two Helen Hayes awards, an Emmy, the Drama Desk award, and the American Express Tribute To An American Actor. He continued to perform on stage and present lectures on his long career at universities, film festivals, for theater benefits, business groups and on cruises. He died on December 8, 2008, in Washington, D.C.
Scope and Content
Consists of documents spanning Prosky's career in theatre, film, and television. Materials include playbills, photographs, scripts, reviews, fan letters, scrapbooks, and audiovisual.
The collection consists of six series. The first series contains documents from his professional career divided into three subseries and arranged alphabetically by play, film, or television title, then chronologically. Subseries 1.1 includes playbills that date from his early performances at the Quarterdeck Theatre to his most recent performances in Washington, D.C. There are also numerous reviews as well as a few scripts with Prosky's handwritten notes. Subseries 1.2 contains mostly clippings and reviews about Prosky's film career, but there are a few scripts and emphemra, such as the trading card from "The Last Action Hero." Subseries 1.3 contains documents from his television career, mostly clippings from his time as a cast member on "Hill Street Blues" and "Veronica's Closet." Note that there are additional professional documents, such as posters, in the oversize series.
The second series contains personal documents and is divided into two subseries and arranged alphabetically and chronologically. Subseries 2.1 consists of correspondence to and from Prosky. The bulk of the correspondence concerns Prosky's family and close friends. There are also many greeting cards wishing Prosky luck on opening nights as well as offering congratulations and thanks. Subseries 2.2 contains many biographical articles discussing Prosky's life as an actor. The articles also discuss Prosky's wife and sons. Also contained in the subseries are clippings, programs, and certificates from awards ceremonies that Prosky participated in as a nominee and won. Of particular interest are transcripts from an autobiography by Prosky. Note that there are additional biographical articles in the oversize series both loose and in scrapbooks.
The third series contains photographs of Prosky' professional and personal life. Many of the photographs document Prosky's theatre and film career. There are also photographs from his personal life, such as family snapshots. The photographs range in size from 3"x5" to 8"x10". Most of the theatre and professional photographs are larger and in black and white while the personal snapshots are smaller and in color. Arranged by category, then production title or other description, and then arranged chronologically. Note that there are additional photographs in the oversize series both loose and in scrapbooks.
The fourth series consists of copies of Prosky's film and television appearances, particularly "Veronica's Closet." There are also copies of public service announcements and commercials. Most of the media contained on VHS cassettes and reel-to-reel audio tapes. There are also DVD copies of speaking engagements at George Mason University and other locations.
The fifth series contains items too large for the other series. Included are photographs, scrapbooks, and posters documenting Prosky's professional career and personal life.
The sixth series consists of objects from Prosky's professional career and personal life, such as opening night gifts and production souvenirs.
Arrangement
Organized into six series:
Series 1: Professional, 1954-2007 (Boxes 1-5)
Series 2: Personal, 1909-2007 (Boxes 5-8)
Series 3: Photographs, 1930s-2005 (Boxes 9-11)
Series 4: Audiovisual, 1960-2007 (Boxes 12-13)
Series 5: Oversize, 1950s-2006 (Boxes 14-15)
Series 6: Realia, 1998-2004 (Box 16)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds the.
Index Terms
Persons:
Prosky, Robert, 1930-
Corporate Names:
Arena Stage (Organization: Washington, D.C.)
Subjects:
Actors--United States.; Motion pictures--United States.; Television--United States.; Theater--United States.; Theater--Washington (D.C.)
Contents List
- Series 1: Professional, 1954-2007, (5 boxes)
  Contains documents from his professional career divided into three subseries and arranged alphabetically by play, film, or television title, then chronologically.
  - Subseries 1.1: Theater, 1954-2007, (2.5 boxes)
    Includes playbills that date from his early performances at the Quarterdeck Theatre to his most recent performances in Washington, D.C. There are also numerous reviews as well as a few scripts with Prosky's handwritten notes.
    - "An American Daughter" Printed Material, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Arena Stage. Contains press releases, reviews, and Arena Stage publications.
    - American Film Institute Preview Program Guide, March 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Anniversary Waltz, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Arthur Miller Theatre Reviews, 1983-2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - "Awake and Sing" Printed Material, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Awake and Sing" Playbill, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Arena Stage.
    - Arena Stage 30th Anniversary Season Annual Report, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Arena Stage Production History, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - "Bad Seed" Playbill, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Quarterdeck Theatre.
    - "Barnum" Playbill, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Gonzaga College. Prosky not in cast.
    - "Battle Dream" Playbill, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "Camping with Henry and Tom" Playbill, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Lucille Lortel Theatre.
    - "Camping with Henry and Tom" Review, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Berkshire Theatre Festival. Review by Herbert Wolff.
    - "Camping with Henry and Tom" Reviews, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The Best of Broadway Newspaper Article, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - "Caucasian Chalk Circle" Reviews, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - "The Chase" Playbill, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Old Academy.
    - "Dear Charles" Playbill, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - "Death of a Salesman" Reviews, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - "A Delicate Balance" Playbill, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - "Democracy" Playbill, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Brooks Atkinson Theatre.
    - "Democracy" Script, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - "The Dybbuk" Reviews, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - "Galileo" Review, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Arena Stage. Review by Mel Gussow.
    - "Inherit the Wind" Reviews, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Ford's Theatre.
    - General Theatre Reviews, 1971-2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Also contains television reviews and biographical information.
    - "Glengarry Glen Ross" Playbill, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Goodman Theatre.
    - "Glengarry Glen Ross" Playbill, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      John Golden Theatre.
    - "Glengarry Glen Ross" Clippings, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "The Golem" Clippings, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Manhattan Ensemble Theater. Also contains postcards with advertisements.
    - "The Happy Time" Playbill, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Fred Miller Theatre.
    - "The Hollow" Playbill, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Hong Kong Arts Festival, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Inherit the Wind" Playbill, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "Inherit the Wind" Reviews, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - "A Life in the Theatre" Flyer, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Lee Strasberg Theatre Center.
    - "The Matchmaker" Reviews, 1993, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Delaware Theatre Company (1993) and Arena Stage (1995).
    - "Moonchildren" Poster, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Douglass College.
    - "Moonchildren" Press Releases, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - "Noises Off" Research Packet, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - "Noises Off" Script, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - "Picnic" Playbill, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - "The Price" Playbill, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Morosco Theatre. Prosky not in cast.
    - "The Price" Playbill, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - "The Price" Playbill, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Gate Theatre.
    - "The Price" Poster, 2004? (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Cape May Stage.
    - "The Price" Reviews, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Arena Stage. Also contains a pre-production announcement.
    - "The Seven Year Itch" Playbill, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - "Shakespeare in Hollywood" Printed Material, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - A Short History of the Booth Theatre, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - "Sketches of War" Flyer, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Colonial Theatre.
    - "The Solid Gold Cadillac" Playbill, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Three Men on a Horse" Review, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Twelfth Night" Press Release, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "A View from the Bridge" Playbill, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Coronet Theatre. Prosky not in cast.
    - "A View from the Bridge" Playbill, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Ambassador Theatre.
    - "A View from the Bridge" Playbill, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Royal Poinciana Playhouse. Prosky not in cast.
    - "A Walk in the Woods" Playbill, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Booth Theatre.
    - "A Walk in the Woods" Playbill, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      One copy entirely in Russian and one with only the title translated.
    - "A Walk in the Woods" Reviews, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Booth Theatre. Also contains some correspondence.
    - "A Walk in the Woods" Script, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Washington Theatre Review, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Contains stories on Zelda Fichandler and Robert Prosky.
    - "Will Success Spoil Rock Hunter?" Playbill, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "You Can't Take It with You" Playbill, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Hong Kong Arts Festival.
    - "You Can't Take It with You" Playbill, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Guthrie Theatre.
    - "You Can't Take It with You" Postcard, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - "You Can't Take It with You" Reviews, 1979-1980, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Also contains advertisements, rosters, and announcements.
  - Subseries 1.2: Film, 1980-2007, (1.5 boxes)
    Contains mostly clippings and reviews about Prosky's film career, but there are also a few scripts and emphemra, such as the trading card from "The Last Action Hero."
    - "Broadcast News" Reviews, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Casting Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - "Christine" Poster, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - "City of Ember" Script, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Also contains correspondence.
    - "Grandfather's Birthday" Printed Material, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Contains production facts, one color production still photograph, and one black and white photograph of the director Gayle Knutson.
    - "Last Action Hero" Trading Card, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "Lords of Discipline" Clippings, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "Mrs. Doubtfire" Script, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "The Natural" Clipping, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Also includes information on "Glengarry Glenn Ross" and television work.
    - The New Jersey State Film Festival, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "The Thief" Reviews, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "The Thief" Script, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "Things Change" Clipping, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - "Washington Monuments" review, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.3: Television, 1984-2007, (1.5 boxes)
    Contains documents from his television career, mostly clippings from his time as a cast member on "Hill Street Blues" and "Veronica's Closet."
    - "ER: Family Business" Script, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - "Frasier: A Cranes' Critique" Script, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - "Hill Street Blues" Clippings, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - "Hill Street Blues" Clippings, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - "Home Fires Burning" Press Releases and Clippings, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "Into Thin Air" Review, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "The Murder of Mary Phagan" Clippings and Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Old Dogs" Clippings and Reviews, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - "The Practice" Clipping, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Veronica's Closet" Clippings, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Veronica's Closet" Production Directory and Publicity Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Series 2: Personal, 1909-2007, (4 boxes)
  The second series contains personal documents and is divided into two subseries and arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
  - Subseries 2.1: Correspondence, 1909-2007, (1.5 boxes)
    Subseries 2.1 consists of correspondence to and from Prosky. The bulk of the correspondence concerns Prosky's family and close friends. There are also many greeting cards wishing Prosky luck on opening nights as well as offering congratulations and thanks. Arranged alphabetically by name type of correspondence, then chronologically.
    - Aunt Vi, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Casey, Phil, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Family and Friends, 1978-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Fan Letters, 1978-1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Fichandler, Zelda, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Greeting Cards, 1980s-2006 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Law, Lindsay, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984-2007 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Postcards, 1909, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Opening Night Cards, 1987-2006 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - A Proposal for a Trust for the Acting Company of Arena Stage, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Prosky Family, 1990-1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Sasser, Bill, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Schatz Orstein Studios, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Thank You Cards, 1988-2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Thief", 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Universal Studios, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      RESTRICTED
    - Vinograd, Marty, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - "A Walk in the Woods", 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Also includes correspondence about Prosky's Tony Award nomination.
    - Washington Post, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2.2: Biographical, 1967-2007, (2.5 boxes)
    Contains many biographical articles discussing Prosky's life as an actor. The articles also discuss Prosky's wife and sons. Also contained in the subseries are clippings, programs, and certificates from awards ceremonies that Prosky participated in as a nominee and won. This subseries also contains transcripts from a self-recorded autobiography by Prosky. Arranged alphabetically by article title and type of document, then chronologically.
    - "Actor Bob Prosky - Johnny Haas Relatives", 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Post Eagle newspaper.
    - "Ah, Prosky!", 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Columbia Flier newspaper.
    - "An American Actor", 1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      America 275 Illustrated Story no. 11-79.
    - Antoinette Perry (Tony) Awards Playbill, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Prosky nominated for "Glengarry Glenross"."
    - Antoinette Perry (Tony) Awards Playbill, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Prosky nominated for "A Walk in the Woods".
    - Atlantic City Film Festival Award Certificate, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Prosky won best actor in a short film for "Grandfather's Birthday".
    - Autobiographical Text, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Biography Draft 1, ca. 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Biography Draft 2, ca. 2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Folder 1.
    - Biography Draft 2, ca. 2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Folder 2.
    - Biography of Robert Prosky, ca. 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Cynthia Snyder Public Relations.
    - Birthday Scrapbook, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Bob Prosky: Twenty Years of Arena Stage", 1970s (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Article by Zelda Fichandler.
    - Cafe du Soleil Celebrity Recipes, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Cafe du Soleil Celebrity Recipes, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Career Clippings, 1967-1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Career Chronology and Credits, ca. 2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Celebrity of the Day", 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Charity Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Cosmos Club Certificate of Appreciation, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Presented to both Prosky and his wife Ida.
    - "An Evening with Robert Prosky" Invitation, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "The Friends of George Spelvin" Pamphlet, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "The Grocer's Kid", 1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Philadelphia magazine.
    - The Helen Hayes Award, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Prosky served as the master of ceremonies.
    - The Helen Hayes Award, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Prosky nominated for his role in "Our Town".
    - The Helen Hayes Award, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Prosky honored with the American Express Tribute.
    - "He's Made a Career of Being an Old Man", 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Washington Post newspaper.
    - "He's Quite a Character", 1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Roxborough Times newspaper.
    - "Hill St. Dad visits new RU grad", 1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Home News newspaper.
    - "Hoffman: A Fresh Face Even as Age Catches Up", 1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      New York Times Newspaper.
    - "I Don't Know What I'm Doing", 1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Equity News newsletter.
    - "In Russia He Heard No One Cry Out", 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      New York Times newspaper.
    - Jewish Council on Aging Acceptance Speech, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "A Life in the Spotlight: An Afternoon with Robert Prosky" Program, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "A Life in the Spotlight: An Evening with Robert Prosky" Program, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - List of Accomplishments, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Local Interest Clippings, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Artwork and Stamps, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1973-2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1973-2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Television Broadcasters Award, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Presented to Prosky for his role as Mr. Buchanan in "Jabberwocky".
    - "N. Va.'s Theater Scene is Flourishing", 1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Sun Weekly newspaper.
    - Notes for Class Taught at Arena Stage, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "On the Move", 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      People Weekly magazine.
    - Ovation Awards Nomination Certificate, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Prosky's Most Recent Credits, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Prosky, Ida, Job Description, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Resumes, 1970s-1980s (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - "Robert Prosky: Distinguished Actor", 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Relax magazine. In Polish.
    - "Robert Prosky: Hey...Don't I Know You?", 2006 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      New Jersey Lifestyle magazine.
    - "Robert Prosky: Performer and Penmaker Extraordinaire", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Pen World magazine.
    - "Robert Prosky: The Actor Struts and Frets", 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Washington Post Magazine.
    - Rutgers Press Release, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "The Sarge and His Son", 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Daily News newspaper.
    - "The Sayings of Director Joe", n.d. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "Second Stage: Washington's Own Robert Prosky Finds a New Arena in Hollywood", 1987 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      Dossier magazine.
    - "Signature, First Amendment Rule", 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      Washington Times newspaper. Article mentions Prosky's Hayes award for "The Price".
    - Sketches and Magazine Photograph of Prosky, 1980s (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - "Theatrical Prosky Family Together Here or on Stage", 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Tony Awards Clippings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      Also includes correspondence.
- Series 3: Photographs, 1930s-2005, (3 boxes)
  Contains photographs of Prosky' professional and personal life. Many of the photographs document Prosky's theatre and film career. There are also photographs from his personal life, such as family snapshots. The photographs range in size from 3"x5" to 8"x10". Most of the theatre and professional photographs are larger and in black and white while the personal snapshots are smaller and in color. Arranged by category, then production title or other description, and then arranged chronologically.
  - Appearances, "Dedication of Kreeger Stage", 1970s (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Appearances, "Hands Across America", 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Appearances, [Hands Across America. St. Patrick's Day. Washington D.C.], 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Appearances, Parade, 1980s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Appearances, [Prosky speaking at Credit Union National Assoc. Inc.], 1980s (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Appearances, Sardi's, 1980s (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Appearances, [Stop Arthritis Telethon], 1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Appearances, Tim Conway Golf Classic, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Appearances, [Unidentified], 1980s (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Appearances, [Unidentified], 1980s (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Appearances, "A View From the Bridge" [Opening Night after Theatre Supper], February 3, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Appearances, "WYKS" [Hyatt Regency Washington D.C.], 1980s (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Commercials, "Central Charge Credit Card" 1970s (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Commercials, [Unidentified], 1970s (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Commercials, Volkswagen and men from Arena Stage, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Film, "Age Isn't Everything" [Original title "Life in the Food Chain"], 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Film, "Brother's Destiny", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Film, "The Chamber", 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Film, "Christine", 1983 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Film, "Dudley Do-Right", 1999 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Film, "Far and Away", 1992 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Film, "Funny About Love", 1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Film, "Grandfather's Birthday" [Theatre Photo], 2001 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Film, "Gremlins II", 1990 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Film, "Hanky Panky", 1982 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Film, "Hoffa", 1992 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Film, "The Keep", 1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Film, "Lords of Discipline", 1983 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Film, "Mrs. Doubtfire", 1993 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Film, "The Natural"; [Baseball Hall of Fame Donation], 1984 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Film, "The Scarlet Letter", 1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Film, "Thief", 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Film, "Two Thanksgiving Gentlemen", 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)